const STORE = [
    { 
        question: "What was Pac-Man's original English name?",
        answers: [
            "Puck-Man",
            "Disc-Man",
            "Pac-Man",
            "Ghost-Man"
        ],
        rightAnswer: "Puck-Man",
        extraInfo: "People scratched the P to make an F, so they changed the name."
    },  
    { 
        question: "Atari founder Nolan Bushnell also created which business?",
        answers: [
            "Hasbro",
            "Activision",
            "Chuck E. Cheese's",
            "Dave & Buster's"
        ],
        rightAnswer: "Chuck E. Cheese's",
        extraInfo: "He had a ban from designing games, so he created a way to still profit from the game industry."
    },
    { 
        question: "Which of the following is not an Xbox exclusive?",
        answers: [
            "Halo",
            "Cuphead",
            "Gears of War",
            "Forza"
        ],
        rightAnswer: "Cuphead",
        extraInfo: "It's now available on the Nintendo Switch."
    },
    { 
        question: "Which was not a character in the original Super Smash Bros?",
        answers: [
            "Pikachu",
            "Kirby",
            "Ness",
            "Bowser"
        ],
        rightAnswer: "Bowser",
        extraInfo: "He wasn't added until Super Smash Bros Melee."
    },
    { 
        question: "Which video game company did Steve Jobs work at?",
        answers: [
            "Sega",
            "Nintendo",
            "Electronic Arts",
            "Atari"
        ],
        rightAnswer: "Atari",
        extraInfo: "He designed the game Breakout while at Atari."
    },
    { 
        question: "How many Tetris pieces are there?",
        answers: [
            "Five",
            "Six",
            "Seven",
            "Eight"
        ],
        rightAnswer: "Seven",
        extraInfo: "There's a T, S, Z, L, backwards L, the line, and the square."
    },
    { 
        question: "Nintendo was originally founded to create what?",
        answers: [
            "Dice",
            "Radios",
            "Computers",
            "Playing cards"
        ],
        rightAnswer: "Playing cards",
        extraInfo: "They were founded in 1889 and still release playing cards today."
    },
    { 
        question: "Which franchise did Shigeru Miyamoto not create?",
        answers: [
            "Metroid",
            "Mario",
            "Donkey Kong",
            "Zelda"
        ],
        rightAnswer: "Metroid",
        extraInfo: "He still helped work on the series though."
    },
    { 
        question: "Tomb Raider's Laura Croft originally had which last name?",
        answers: [
            "Craft",
            "Cruz",
            "Creed",
            "Crabbe"
        ],
        rightAnswer: "Cruz",
        extraInfo: "They decided they wanted a different race for the character."
    },
    { 
        question: "The UK edition of FIFA 2001 included which feature?",
        answers: [
            "A scratch and sniff disc to smell the pitch",
            "A contest to become a Premier League player in real life",
            "Discounted tickets to the EFL Cup final",
            "A piece of a game-worn jersey"
        ],
        rightAnswer: "A scratch and sniff disc to smell the pitch",
        extraInfo: "Gran Turismo 2 also had this feature."
    }
];